DANILO RIBEIRO

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

DETAILS

ADDRESS

Rua Mario Eduardo Serra Lima, 265 Pouso Alegre, 37.558-455 Brazil

PHONE

+55 35 99846 5456

PLACE OF BIRTH

February 15th 1984 São Paulo

NATIONALITY

Brazilian

LINKS

GITHUB - github.com/dmax101

LINKEDIN - linkedin.com/in/danribeiro101/

SKILLS

JAVASCRIPT / TYPESCRIPT

ANGULAR

• • • • •

JAVA

 $\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ \circ$

PYTHON

HTML & CSS

••••

C++

• • • • •

● ● ● ○ ○

NODE.JS

GITHUB

 $\bullet \bullet \circ \circ \circ$

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH



PROFILE

Dedicated Developer with passion to identify and solve problems. Ability to establish and maintain a good communication and relationships with team. Committed to utilizing my skills to further the mission of a company. Experienced with the latest cutting edge development tools and procedures.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Frontend Developer at Deloitte

Nov, 2021 - actual - São Paulo (remote)

I actualy work with Angular (Typescript) in a development of a solution at Deloitte.

Frontend Developer and UI Designer at Limonada Comunicação

Mar, 2008 - Mar, 2017 - São Paulo

I worked with interactive digital publishing for tablets using Javascript and motion graphics using CSS and After Effects, as well I had experience with development of wireframes and online materials.

EDUCATION

Computer Engineering at Instituto Nacional de Telecomunicações

Jul, 2017 - Present - Santa Rita do Sapucaí

The course allows me to work in the areas of software development, firmware and hardware, app development and I also had experience with Artificial Intelligence and IOT.

Advertising and Marketing

Jul, 2009 - Dec, 2012 - São Paulo

Advertising: customer service, planning, creation and media; Marketing: management of marketing and products, strategic planning, market research and sales administration, with regard to marketing activities.

INTERNSHIPS

TI Support at Instituto Nacional de Telecomunicações

Sep, 2018 - Sep, 2019 - Santa Rita do Sapucaí

I acted as customer support helping to solve several problems and working with Active Directory and Powershell.

Frontend at Dágora

Mar, 2018 - Sep, 2018 - Santa Rita do Sapucaí

I perform developing e-mails marketings with Ink framework.

EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

Artificial Intelligence Scholarship at Instituto Nacional de Telecomunicações

May, 2020 - Apr, 2021 - Santa Rita do Sapucaí

I developed a voice assistant app using artificial intelligence with Wit.ai, React Native and Java to control a bunch of devices inside laboratory using MQTT protocol over SSL.